<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<topiclist>
	<topic id="2011-001">
		<title>Who is the head of CloudCrowd?</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must explicitly state that the CEO of CloudCrowd is Alex Edelstein. It is not sufficient if they indicate him as the founder.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may contain information regarding Alex Edelstein, CloudCrowd’s CEO or state him as the founder, but it does not explicitly say he is the CEO.</level>
			<level value="0">the document is not related to the CEO. It may still be related to CloudCrowd, but not to its CEO.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-002">
		<title>Methods of quality control in crowdsourcing</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must discuss methods or techniques for quality control in crowdsourcing tasks, such as CrowdFlower’s gold units.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may discuss the need for quality control or cases where it is applied, but does not provide details no how it is done.</level>
			<level value="0">the document discusses the use of crowdsourcing for quality control as opposed to quality control in crowdsourcing.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-003">
		<title>Who invented the Mechanical Turk?</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must explicitly name Wolfgang von Kempelen as the inventor of the Mechanical Turk chess-playing machine.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may talk about the chess-playing machine, but it does not state von Kempelen as the inventor.</level>
			<level value="0">the document is not related to the chess-playing machine but to Amazon’s crowdsourcing platform or it is not related to Mechanical Turk at all.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-004">
		<title>Workshops and conferences related to crowdsourcing</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must list or discuss at least one academic venue (workshop, conference, congress, symposium, etc.) where crowdsourcing is the main topic.</level>
			<level value="1">the document lists or discusses academic venues where crowdsourcing is not the main topic, but they include papers or talks about it.</level>
			<level value="0">the document contains information about the use of crowdsourcing in conferences, or it is just not related at all to conferences on crowdsourcing.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-005">
		<title>Music projects funded with crowdfunding</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must explicitly mention music projects, bands or artists that have been funded via crowdfunding.</level>
			<level value="1">the document discusses companies that provide crowdfunding services for music projects, but it does not mention particular cases.</level>
			<level value="0">the document may contain information about companies providing crowdfunding services, but it does not mention direct application to music projects.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-006">
		<title>Who founded CrowdFlower?</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must state that both Lukas Biewald and Chris Van Pelt founded Crowdflower.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may mention either Biewald or Van Pelt as founder, but not both.</level>
			<level value="0">the document may still mention either Biewald as CEO or Van Pelts as CTO, but it does not mention them being founders of the company.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-007">
		<title>Who and where used the term crowdsourcing for the first time?</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must explicitly state that Jeff Howe coined the term crowdsourcing in a June 2006 article in the Wired magazine.</level>
			<level value="1">the document mentions Jeff Howe but not the Wired article.</level>
			<level value="0">the document may be related to Jeff Howe, the Wired magazine or crowdsourcing, but it does not fully and explicitly answer the question.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-008">
		<title>Tips for requesters in Amazon Mechanical Turk</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must list or discuss tips or guidelines for requesters in Mechanical Turk, but not for workers.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may list or discuss tips for Mechanical Turk workers.</level>
			<level value="0">the document does not provide any insight into the best practices in Mechanical Turk.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-009">
		<title>Motivation behind crowdsourcing workers</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must discuss motivations behind workers of crowdsourcing platforms, and present quantitative data obtained with experiments, surveys, etc.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may discuss or list motivations for crowdsourcing workers, but it does not provide any quantitative data.</level>
			<level value="0">the document may discuss motivations to request work in crowdsourcing platforms, but it does not provide any insight as to the motivations for workers.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-010">
		<title>reCAPTCHA usage statistics</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must contain some global statistics on the usage of reCAPTCHA to control access in websites, digitization of books, etc.</level>
			<level value="1">the document contains usage statistics of reCAPTCHA in some particular website or tool, but not globally.</level>
			<level value="0">the document may contain information on how to use reCAPTCHA in a website, but it does not provide any usage statistics.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-011">
		<title>Top 10 companies providing crowdsourcing services</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must list and discuss at least 10 companies or websites that provide crowdsourcing services, such as Amazon Mechanical Turk or CrowdFlower.</level>
			<level value="1">the document contains a list of crowdsourcing sites, but it does not discuss why they are the top 10.</level>
			<level value="0">the document lists companies that do not provide crowdsourcing services, but rather companies that use them.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-012">
		<title>Results of the Galaxy Zoo project</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must contain quantitative information about the results of the project, such as number of galaxies tagged, how many people has participated, etc.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may contain information as to the expected results of the project, but it does not mention any information of the progress.</level>
			<level value="0">the document may be related to Galaxy Zoo, but it does not provide any insight about the results of the project.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-013">
		<title>Use of crowdsourcing in Information Retrieval</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must list or discuss case studies of crowdsourcing applied in Information Retrieval, such as the use for relevance judging.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may comment on areas of Information Retrieval where crowdsourcing can be applied, but it does not contain information on particular case studies where it has been done.</level>
			<level value="0">the document is not related to the application of crowdsourcing in Information Retrieval.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-014">
		<title>Use of gold units in CrowdFlower</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must explain what gold units are in Crowdflower and give tips on how they are used for quality control.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may explain what gold units are, but it does not mention how they are used or should be used.</level>
			<level value="0">the document may mention gold units but it does not explain what they are.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-015">
		<title>Companies using crowdsourcing services</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document contains information on companies that use crowdsourcing services, mentioning what they use it for.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may list companies using crowdsourcing, but it does not provide information as to the tasks being carried out.</level>
			<level value="0">the document may discuss companies related to crowdsourcing, but not companies actually using crowdsourcing services.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-016">
		<title>Crowdsourcing sites for logo design</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must list or contain information about crowdsourcing websites specialized in logo design.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may discuss logo design through crowdsourcing, but it does not provide information on particular sites.</level>
			<level value="0">the document may relate to crowdsourcing or logo design, but it is not related to crowdsourcing logos at all.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-017">
		<title>How to create qualification tests in Mechanical Turk</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must explain what qualification tests are in Mechanical Turk and give step by step guidelines on how they are created.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may explain what qualification tests are and what they are used for, but it does not actually explain how they are used.</level>
			<level value="0">the document may mention what qualification tests are but it does not provide any insight on their use.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-018">
		<title>Who won the 2009 DARPA balloon network challenge?</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must list all members of the MIT red balloon challenge team: Sandy Pentland, Manuel Cebrian, Anmol Madan, Galen Pickard, Riley Crane, Wei Pan.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may list some of the members or just mention the MIT group alone.</level>
			<level value="0">the document does not specify who won the challenge, neither people nor group.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-019">
		<title>Open source platforms for crowdsourcing</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must list some open source frameworks or platforms to help in managing crowdsourcing tasks.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may list frameworks that are not open source or comment on the need for open source platforms.</level>
			<level value="0">the document may still discuss the need for frameworks, but does not mention anything about open source.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-020">
		<title>Use of crowdsourcing in Machine Learning</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must list or discuss case studies of crowdsourcing applied in Machine Learning, such as the use for labeling training data sets.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may comment on the use of crowdsourcing for Machine Learning, but it does not contain information on particular case studies where it has been done.</level>
			<level value="0">the document is not related to the application of crowdsourcing in Machine Learning.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-021">
		<title>Use of crowdsourcing in Natural Language Processing</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must list or discuss case studies of crowdsourcing applied in Natural Language Processing, such as the use for tagging named entities.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may comment on areas of Natural Language Processing where crowdsourcing can be applied, but it does not contain information on particular case studies where it has been done.</level>
			<level value="0">the document is not related to the application of crowdsourcing in Natural Language Processing.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-022">
		<title>Crowdsourcing for satellite image analysis</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document discusses case studies where crowdsourcing is used to analyze satellite imagery, such as in disaster response control.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may discuss how crowdsourcing could be used for satellite image analysis, but it does not give real cases where it is applied.</level>
			<level value="0">the document may be related to crowdsourcing for image analysis, but not satellite images in particular.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
	<topic id="2011-023">
		<title>Who invented the ESP game?</title>
		<relevance>
			<level value="2">the document must explicitly name Luis von Ahn as the inventor of the ESP game. used to label images.</level>
			<level value="1">the document may mention von Ahn, but it does not explicitly indicate him as the creator.</level>
			<level value="0">the document is not related to the ESP game to label images, but others related, such as TagATune.</level>
		</relevance>
	</topic>
</topiclist>